<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-04-18T18:23:15-07:00</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">TODO</title><subtitle></subtitle><entry><title type="html">A Year in Review</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2020/04/17/a-year-in-review.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Year in Review" /><published>2020-04-17T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-04-17T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2020/04/17/a-year-in-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2020/04/17/a-year-in-review.html">&lt;p&gt;As someone who has for a long time wanted to:
A) become a better writer
B) have engaging conversations
C) start a blog &lt;strong&gt;and&lt;/strong&gt;
D) put something of substance on this webpage,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;it seems like now is the economically sensible time to write something. Quarantine has the click supply at an all time high. So here goes -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-python&quot; data-lang=&quot;python&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;print&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;Hello, world!&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The earliest memory I have of 2019 available at simple recall was a day long &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Agile_software_development&quot;&gt;agile&lt;/a&gt; workshop. If you don’t know what agile is… prepare for &lt;em&gt;enlightenment&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, I was so &lt;em&gt;enlightened&lt;/em&gt; that I booked a red-eye flight to Cancún to see Dead and Company with a couple of coworkers. This was mid-January - we’ll say the year started here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I saw Dead and company 13 times last year. It took me the whole year to figure out why I like live music - but maybe that’s because my whole reason is the years worth of live music I’ve seen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of my favorite shows? The Gorge Amphitheater was beautiful. Celebrating New Year’s with my family at the Chase Center was a quintessentially &lt;em&gt;us&lt;/em&gt; thing to do. The venue in Cancún is also really amazing - warm weather and wind are two things I love. And for anyone who isn’t familiar with Dead and Company/The Grateful Dead - they are &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; jam band. Each rendition of a song is different, and quite often substantially so. In fact, it’s common for concert-goers to try to guess what song is being played or led into, sometimes even minutes in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am grateful for the opportunities presented to me to travel around and hear this music. Attending live music with friends is something I plan to keep doing. Part of the experience is the venue. Part of it is the trip. Part of it is the music. The songs stick with you in a way that I’m not convinced they otherwise would. You hear new music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of concerts, I also went to Outside Lands for the third time (Paul Simon was there!), and Coachella for the first time. I saw John Mayer at the Chase Center in San Francisco. 2019 was really the most live music I have ever attended.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m also now officially becoming a scientist! I put my first preprint on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/2001.02779&quot;&gt;arXiv&lt;/a&gt;. I presented at &lt;a href=&quot;http://meetings.aps.org/Meeting/MAR19/Session/X35.10&quot;&gt;March Meeting&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://physics.unm.edu/SQuInT/2020/abstracts.php?person_id=1075&quot;&gt;SQuInT&lt;/a&gt;. I’ve found two amazing advisors to pursue a Ph.D. with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2019 was not an easy year. My relationship of nine years came to an end. I lost two grandparents and my relationship with one of my closest friends became untenable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2019 was a year of change. I left my first job to pursue a Ph.D. I left California, my home of twenty five years, and moved to Colorado.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2019 was my most challenging year so far. I have been depressed and anxious, and not myself. But that doesn’t make it bad year. I learned a lot -  I’m still learning a lot - and that’s the only way forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Growth is really, really hard. But growth is really, really great. Thanks to all my friends for growing with me, and thanks for spending your time reading this. I hope we can see each other again soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay Healthy,
Anthony&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">As someone who has for a long time wanted to: A) become a better writer B) have engaging conversations C) start a blog and D) put something of substance on this webpage,</summary></entry></feed>