<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-06-10T14:37:07-06:00</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">TODO</title><subtitle></subtitle><entry><title type="html">A Year in Review</title><link href="/2020/04/26/a-year-in-review.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Year in Review" /><published>2020-04-26T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2020-04-26T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>/2020/04/26/a-year-in-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/04/26/a-year-in-review.html">&lt;p&gt;As someone who has for a long time wanted to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A) become a better writer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;B) have engaging conversations&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;C) start a blog &lt;strong&gt;and&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;D) put something of substance on this webpage,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;it seems like now is the economically sensible time to write something. Quarantine has the click supply at an all time high. I’m hoping this blog will serve as a public-facing journal that will help me reflect with intention, and a place for me to write notes about things I find interesting. My current model for this site is a bulletin board that I can invite all my friends to come look at. But in this first post, I’ll focus on just getting things off the ground. So here goes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-python&quot; data-lang=&quot;python&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;print&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;Hello, world!&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll open with talking about 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The earliest memory I have of 2019 was a day long &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Agile_software_development&quot;&gt;agile&lt;/a&gt; workshop at work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That same day, invigorated by my newfound passion for scrum, I booked a redeye flight to Cancún to see &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dead_%26_Company&quot;&gt;Dead &amp;amp; Company&lt;/a&gt; with a couple of coworkers. In what can &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; be described as a demonstration of devotion, I saw Dead &amp;amp; Company 13 times last year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, last year was a really big year for me as far as music goes - Dead &amp;amp; Company, Coachella, John Mayer, Outside Lands, Bon Iver, Rainbow Kitten Suprise, Mt. Joy, Denver Comes Alive, and Hippocampus. I never really understood why people see live music before last year - and I’m not going to claim to understand it now - but I will say that I’m going to keep seeing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year was a big year for travel! I went to Cancún, Lisbon, Madrid, Barcelona, Amsterdam, Paris, Boston and Albuquerque. I also did a bit of camping - Redwood National and State Parks and Bishop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year was a good year for sports. Strava says I ran 307 miles, I started snowboarding (Squaw, Winter Park, and Eldora!), and also started surfing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am officially becoming a scientist! You might argue that being a scientist is thing of lifestyle - a dedication to the scientific method. You might argue I was already becoming a scientist at Rigetti. If you don’t argue that, maybe I would. But, more to the point of what I mean: I put my first preprint on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/2001.02779&quot;&gt;arXiv&lt;/a&gt;! I presented at &lt;a href=&quot;http://meetings.aps.org/Meeting/MAR19/Session/X35.10&quot;&gt;March Meeting&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://physics.unm.edu/SQuInT/2020/abstracts.php?person_id=1075&quot;&gt;SQuInT&lt;/a&gt;! I’ve found two amazing advisors (&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/quantum_graeme?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor&quot;&gt;Graeme Smith&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://jila.colorado.edu/arey/&quot;&gt;Ana Maria Rey&lt;/a&gt;) to pursue a Ph.D. in physics with at the University of Colorado, Boulder. I couldn’t be happier that I ended up where I did. (When I applied to graduate school my first time in 2016 I was confident I would never be a physicist - I only applied to mathematics and computer science programs!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2019 was a hard year. My relationship of nine years came to an end. I lost two grandparents. A friendship became untenable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2019 was a year of change. I left my first job to pursue a Ph.D. I left California, my home of twenty five years. I left the Bay Area, my home of seven years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2019 was my most challenging year so far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But 2019 has been an &lt;strong&gt;incredibly&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;productive&lt;/em&gt; year. I learned a lot about myself, and that’s the only way forward. Growth is really, really hard. But growth is really, really great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The past is a funny thing - we have the opportunity to post-select on our favorite parts, and it’s already the result of us trying our best to avoid the worst parts. We can reminisce and miss “the good old days”. But I’m excited for the future, I’m excited for Colorado, and I’m excited for all my new friends to come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been very fortunate to have amazing people in my life to support me. I wouldn’t be where I am, as happy as I am, or as excited to &lt;em&gt;get on with the rest of my life&lt;/em&gt; if it weren’t for all of you. I love you all dearly. Thanks for reading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Anthony&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An implementation detail on the blog - I would be remiss if I didn’t provide some way for people to leave comments. I’ve followed the instructions &lt;a href=&quot;https://aristath.github.io/blog/static-site-comments-using-github-issues-api&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for producing a comments section. My website is built on my machine, and hosted by Github. The website is static, but the way this works is I can include JS that fetch comments from open tickets on my repo. Of course, this means you need a Github account to comment. Gets the job done for now. :)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">As someone who has for a long time wanted to: A) become a better writer B) have engaging conversations C) start a blog and D) put something of substance on this webpage,</summary></entry></feed>