<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-04-19T00:34:44-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">TODO</title><subtitle></subtitle><entry><title type="html">A Year in Review</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/17/a-year-in-review.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Year in Review" /><published>2020-04-17T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-04-17T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/04/17/a-year-in-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/04/17/a-year-in-review.html">&lt;p&gt;As someone who has for a long time wanted to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A) become a better writer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;B) have engaging conversations&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;C) start a blog &lt;strong&gt;and&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;D) put something of substance on this webpage,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;it seems like now is the economically sensible time to write something. Quarantine has the click supply at an all time high. I’m hoping this blog will serve as a public-facing journal and a place for me to write notes about things I find interesting. Anyone who knows me knows I like talking, so my current model for this site is a bulletin board that I can invite all my friends to come look at. But in this first post, I’ll focus on just getting things off the ground. So here goes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-python&quot; data-lang=&quot;python&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;print&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;Hello, world!&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll open with talking about my past year. The earliest memory I have of 2019 was a day long &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Agile_software_development&quot;&gt;agile&lt;/a&gt; workshop at work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This workshop was so &lt;em&gt;enlightening&lt;/em&gt; that I booked a red-eye flight to Cancún to see Dead and Company with a couple of coworkers. This was mid-January, so we’ll say the year started here. In what can only be described a demonstration of the depths of devotion, I saw Dead and company 13 times last year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, last year was a really big year for me as far as music goes - Dead and Company, Coachella, John Mayer, Outside Lands, Bon Iver, Rainbow Kitten Suprise, Mt. Joy and Hippocampus to name a few (that might be everything?).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m also now officially becoming a scientist! I put my first preprint on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/2001.02779&quot;&gt;arXiv&lt;/a&gt;. I presented at &lt;a href=&quot;http://meetings.aps.org/Meeting/MAR19/Session/X35.10&quot;&gt;March Meeting&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://physics.unm.edu/SQuInT/2020/abstracts.php?person_id=1075&quot;&gt;SQuInT&lt;/a&gt;. I’ve found two amazing advisors (&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/quantum_graeme?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor&quot;&gt;Graeme Smith&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://jila.colorado.edu/arey/&quot;&gt;Ana Maria Rey&lt;/a&gt; to pursue a Ph.D. with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2019 was a hard year. My relationship of nine years came to an end. I lost two grandparents. One of my closest friendships became untenable. 2019 was a year of change. I left my first job to pursue a Ph.D. I left California, my home of twenty five years, and moved to Colorado. 2019 was my most challenging year so far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But 2019 has been an incredibly &lt;em&gt;productive&lt;/em&gt; year. I learned a lot about myself, and that’s the only way forward. Growth is really, really hard. But growth is really, really great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been very fortunate to have amazing people in my life to support me. I wouldn’t be where I am, as happy as I am, or as excited to &lt;em&gt;get on with the rest of my life&lt;/em&gt; if it weren’t for all of you. I love you all dearly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An implementation detail - I’ve followed the instructions &lt;a href=&quot;https://aristath.github.io/blog/static-site-comments-using-github-issues-api&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for producing a comments section on here. Normally for a comments section there needs to be something &lt;em&gt;listening&lt;/em&gt; for your comments. I don’t want to leave my computer running, and I don’t want to pay for a server, so my temporary solution is that you can comment on issues on the github repo this is being hosted from. When you reload the webpage, the Javascript will politely ask github for the comments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love you all, I miss you all, and I’m really excited to make this site into something people actually want to look at.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Anthony&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">As someone who has for a long time wanted to: A) become a better writer B) have engaging conversations C) start a blog and D) put something of substance on this webpage,</summary></entry></feed>